[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What does the term \"Phishing\" refer to in cybersecurity?",
    "answers": [
      "A type of malware",
      "A method of social engineering",
      "A hardware vulnerability",
      "Network encryption"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of multi-factor authentication (MFA)?",
    "answers": [
      "Username and password",
      "Fingerprint scan and smart card",
      "Email verification only",
      "Security question and answer"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the purpose of a Firewall in cybersecurity?",
    "answers": [
      "Protecting against physical attacks",
      "Monitoring network traffic",
      "Encrypting data transmissions",
      "Blocking unauthorized access to a network"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What does the term \"Malware\" stand for?",
    "answers": [
      "Malicious Software",
      "Mobile Hardware",
      "Mandatory Firewall",
      "Malformed Network"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which cybersecurity measure involves disguising information to make it unreadable without the appropriate decryption key?",
    "answers": [
      "Hashing",
      "Firewall",
      "Encryption",
      "Authentication"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the purpose of a VPN (Virtual Private Network)?",
    "answers": [
      "Protecting against malware",
      "Securely connecting to a private network over the internet",
      "Monitoring website traffic",
      "Blocking phishing attempts"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the main goal of a DDoS (Distributed Denial of Service) attack?",
    "answers": [
      "Stealing sensitive information",
      "Disrupting or disabling services",
      "Gaining unauthorized access to a system",
      "Spreading malware"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the purpose of a Penetration Test in cybersecurity?",
    "answers": [
      "Testing the strength of physical security measures",
      "Assessing the security of a system by simulating an attack",
      "Encrypting sensitive data",
      "Configuring firewalls"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which cybersecurity concept involves ensuring that only authorized individuals can access specific resources or information?",
    "answers": [
      "Encryption",
      "Authentication",
      "Authorization",
      "Firewalling"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the purpose of regular software updates in cybersecurity?",
    "answers": [
      "Enhancing user interfaces",
      "Improving system performance",
      "Fixing security vulnerabilities",
      "Adding new features"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  }
]
